MARC KHIDRIDGE ZALAMEDA

WEB DEVELOPER

- **(**+63) 966 159 5791
- khdzalameda@gmail.com
- Blk 11, Lot 1, Queen Margareth St., Royale Estates 1, Bulihan, Malolos, Bulacan
- khdzalameda.github.io

SKILLS

- WordPress
- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- Javascript
- Vue JS
- PHP
- WooCommerce
- GIT

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Stella Maris Academy of Malolos 2010 - 2014

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Bulacan State University

2014 - 2018

PROFILE

Consummate WordPress developer with extensive knowledge and professional background in building WordPress CMS websites using defacto standard and custom plugins. Over 4 years of PHP, WordPress, WooCommerce, CSS and Javascript experience. Talented with inbuilt WordPress functions, creating custom post types, and developing custom themes and functions from scratch.

EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Circle Business Consulting

2020 - Present

- Delivered quality commercial websites that met coding standards and cross-browser compatibilities
- Converted WIX, Drupal, Shopify, Magento, and Static websites to WordPress.
- Developed CRM websites using WordPress.
- Thoroughly maintained multiple WordPress and WooCommerce websites.
- Built custom web apps from scratch such as hotel management and reservation system using WordPress.
- Integrated 3rd party APIs and services such as Zoom, Mail Chimp, and AWS with WordPress.
- Managed multiple servers and hosting environments and platforms.
- Developed custom plugins for WordPress.
- Troubleshooted multiple website and plugin problems and cleaned hacked and injected scripts.

MARC KHIDRIDGE ZALAMEDA

WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Virtual Growth Agency

2019 - 2020

- Delivered quality commercial websites that met coding standards and cross-browser compatibilities
- Installed required plugins and additional coding to fit final design and functionality requirements
- Collaborated with Project Managers on project specifications, strategy and execution to build new WordPress pages and update existing ones
- Converted design assets into component-based HTML, CSS and JavaScript

WEB DEVELOPER (WORDPRESS AND LARAVEL)

IConcept Global Advertising, Inc.

2018 - 2020

- Developed company website using Wordpress and by converting designs to HTML code
- Built and styled numerous number of new mobile friendly websites and transitioned old site into mobile-friendly version
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed
- Converted mockups into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON
- Implemented website and integrated solutions into business operations